<training>
<text file="LargeTrain/a1.xml">
 <author id="x9971451464197140"/>
  <body>

Pursuant to <NAME/> Kinner's request, I am attaching our form master netting agreement.  The lawyer who will be working with you is <NAME/> Koehler (713/853-3448; anne_koehler@enron.com).  She is out of the office at a seminar and will be returning on Thursday, November 29.

Please let me know if you have any questions or need anything else.
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a10.xml">
 <author id="904579"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:

Per my voice mail, please:

(1) review the Master Energy Purchase and Sale Agreement dated March 1, 2000 (Section 4.4(d)) between Allegheny Energy Supply Company LLC and <NAME/> Power Marketing, Inc., as amended, for your previously negotiated setoff language, and

(2) please forward a copy of the proposed setoff language to <NAME/> <NAME/> so that he can explain what portion of the provision violates Section 6 of PUHCA.  I will be available for a call at his (and your) convenience.

Thanks.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a100.xml">
 <author id="x711851046421971616"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>, here is the info per our phone conversation earlier today.  Call me with any question you may have.

Regards,
<NAME/> Hyatt
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1000.xml">
 <author id="x1946461945161"/>
  <body>

I am still tracking down the Green Mountain documentation, but here is the documentation for LCRA.  I'll forward the rest when I get it.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1001.xml">
 <author id="446543"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>, sorry I missed your call.  

Tell <NAME/> I am in on Sunday ( assume it will be around 7:00 or so)....pls advise on particulars.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1002.xml">
 <author id="x7599811482146199716151110"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I will be in a meeting during this time.  <NAME/> you be able to sit in on this and decide if we should participate further for our group?

Thanks, <NAME/>.
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1003.xml">
 <author id="676708"/>
  <body>

Praveen,

Change of plans. I shall be able to attend
the meeting of the Advisory Board on Wednesday.


<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1004.xml">
 <author id="601217"/>
  <body>

Greetings:  <NAME/> all's going well in your new venture (or semi-new venture at this point).  You finishing this semester? Anyway, I was reading this press account and was wondering if you new this fellow when you were at Lehman.  If so, any insights?  Sort of an interesting career path.  Say hi to your better half.
Best,
<NAME/>
**************************************************************************************
California Power Authority Taps SFPUC's <NAME/> as New CFO
SAN FRANCISCO -- <NAME/> <NAME/> will soon leave his job with San <NAME/>'s public utility commission to head up finances for California 's newly formed power authority, which is authorized to issue $5 billion in revenue bonds. 
The board of the California Consumer Power and Conservation Financing Authority on Friday selected <NAME/> as its first chief financial officer. He will start in his new position in early November. 
The authority was established earlier this year as a result of the state's energy crisis, and is charged with promoting energy conservation efforts and increasing California 's capacity to generate electricity . 
<NAME/> is currently the assistant general manager of finance and administration at the utility commission, which provides water and sewer services to the city and some neighboring counties, as well as hydroelectric power for San <NAME/> government operations. 
<NAME/> has been at the SFPUC since 1999, overseeing finance, personnel and training, information technology, and customer service. He also helped develop the commission's long-range strategic plan and 10-year capital improvement program, which may eventually entail requests for voters to approve more than $4 billion in bonds. 
<NAME/> worked for a start-up Internet company in Palo Alto from 1996 to 1998 before joining the commission. 
From 1985 to 1996, <NAME/> was an investment banker at Lehman Brothers in San <NAME/>, specializing in financing municipal and state-owned power, water, and wastewater systems, according to a release from the power authority. 
He also managed debt financing, financial planning, investment portfolios, and investor relations while a vice president of corporate finance for the New York Power Authority from 1979 until 1985. He helped develop the authority's first conservation program. 
In his new postion as CFO, <NAME/> will earn $185,000 annually. 
Calls to <NAME/> and the SFPUC seeking comment were not returned by press time.
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1005.xml">
 <author id="x99464635141110"/>
  <body>

I must be jinxed.  <NAME/> and I are leaving for Chicago tomorrow and will be there through the weekend.  So we will not be there on Saturday.  Sorry.  We really wanted to come.  We are going to see the 'Stros play at Wrigley on Thursday afternoon.  It should be fun.  See ya.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1006.xml">
 <author id="904579"/>
  <body>

these are all brokerage files with the broker name in bold on first line and <NAME/> company beneath it

Credit Suisse First Boston / JSB Asset, L.L.C. (red)

Bear Stearns International Limited / <NAME/> North America Corp.  (red)

Goldman Sachs & Co. / <NAME/> Corp.  (red)

Goldman Sachs & Co. / <NAME/> Corp. (blue repo file)
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1007.xml">
 <author id="x959941881469997154"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,
 
I understand that you have approved the request below.  Is this because they are WRA personnel?
 
Thanks.  

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1008.xml">
 <author id="280939"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>, we would like to extend a formal offer to Reagan J. Mathews who is currently working for <NAME/> Broadband.  Please forward the formal documentation to Reagan so that the transfer to East Power can take place.

TJ, if you could find out who Reagan's assistant and HR representative are and fax the documentation to the appropriate persons so that he can join our group.

Let me know if you have any questions.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
X 3-0403
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1009.xml">
 <author id="995484"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

I haven't bought a car yet but I will let you know when I get one. When do we get the stalls in E&Y?

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a101.xml">
 <author id="601217"/>
  <body>

Is there any question?  I'll leave to <NAME/> to structure the deal.  As I recall, Montavano, Shapiro and I usually make up one team, but I'm willing to switch around a bit.
 
Best,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1010.xml">
 <author id="676708"/>
  <body>

http://web.mit.edu/alo/www/
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1011.xml">
 <author id="x169710974661110115"/>
  <body>

You've want Puget Sound for approval to trade east physical power on above list, but <NAME/> Hansen will not approve per note below.
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1012.xml">
 <author id="965194"/>
  <body>

Any news?

I am just thinking I will leave around 1 pm here to go home for a bit. I don't have to be at this party till 7 ish, so if you wanna come hang out or just take a nap, you are welcome to do that.

;)
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1013.xml">
 <author id="x1946461945161"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>,

<NAME/> Postlethwaite, <NAME/> Vinson and Casey Evans all have the title of Associate Director.  <NAME/> Reeves was a manager previously so I assume she is also an Associate Director.

I will be out of the office the rest of this afternoon for a doctor's appointment.  If you need me I will have my cell phone 281-382-5215.

Thanks,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1014.xml">
 <author id="601217"/>
  <body>

Thanks very much for dinner, the guacamole and the company.  I left you a check for the truck window work on the kitchen counter.

(That was the best dinner I've ever had in my entire life!  kidding! :)  )

<NAME/> that you're not getting beat up by your bomb-throwing colleagues.

Best,
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1015.xml">
 <author id="428896"/>
  <body>

by the way congrats on the girl.  Is it going to be <NAME/>?
She is going to be 6.5 feet tall
<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1016.xml">
 <author id="265281"/>
  <body>

<NAME/> & <NAME/> --

Do you have any good points of reference on the history of natural gas restructuring?

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1017.xml">
 <author id="640334"/>
  <body>

I made it back to <NAME/> last night.  Incredible security at the airport in London -- it was a mob scene.  In addition to the usual stuff there was an additional search of all carry-ons by hand at the gate and all passengers were patted down by a guard before entering the gate.  I saw several passengers questioned on the plane about their checked luggage -- I couldn't really hear what it was all about.  We were delayed about two and a half hours but it made it feel a little safer.  The Brits were all very nice of course while I was in London but it sure is good to be home.
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1018.xml">
 <author id="904579"/>
  <body>

<NAME/>:  Please send your usual message on this one as well.  There are several written agreements involved.  Thanks.  <NAME/>
</body>
</text>

<text file="LargeTrain/a1019.xml">
 <author id="676708"/>
  <body>

Rakesh,

I don't think I have to be involved.

<NAME/>
</body>
</text>


</training>